Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Faculty and Research Interests, University of Pittsburgh School of Engineering, 1987 (Box 49, Item 13)
- CIT Engineering News, 1986 (Box 49, Item 14)
- Pittsburgh High Technology, 1986 (Box 49, Item 15)
- Pittsburgh Applied Research Corporation: Pilot Plant and Analytical Services (Box 49, Item 16)
- Pittsburgh High Technology Council (Box 49, Item 17)
- Arthur Anderson & Co.: An Entrepreneur's Guide to Starting a Business (Box 49, Item 18)
- Emerging Business Services: Business Plan Checklist by Coopers & Lybrand (Box 49, Item 19)
- Writing a Business Plan by Duquesne University's Small Busines Development Center, 1987 (Box 49, Item 20)
- Development by Allegheny County Department of Development, 1989 (Box 49, Item 21)
- Public-Private Institutions and Advanced Technology Development in Southwestern Pennsylvania by Roger S. Ahlbrandt, Jr. and Clyde Weaver, 1987 (Box 49, Item 22)
- Community Economics, 1988 (Box 49, Item 23)
- 501(c)(3) Monthly Letter, February 1988 (Box 49, Item 24)
- The Foundation Center Publications Catalog, 1989 (Box 49, Item 25)
- Guide to the Programs and Services of Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Item 26)
- Developing the Public Economy: Models from Massachusetts by Pat McGuigan and Bob Schaeffer (Box 49, Item 27)
- Building United Judgment: A Handbook for Consensus Decision Making by the Center for Conflict Resolution (Box 49, Item 28)
- Entrepreneurs Day, Legal Issues Workshop, November 14, 1989 (Box 49, Item 29)
- The South Pittsburgh Reporter, September 27, 1988 (Box 49, Item 30)
- Centennial Reports, 1988 (Box 49, Item 31-33)
- Workers as Owners by the Labor Research Review, 1985 (Box 49, Item 34)
- Jobs & Security: A Grassroots Strategy for Pennsylvania by Pamela Haines (Box 49, Item 35)
- Starting Your Own Business: Answers to Some of Your Questions, 1988 (Box 49, Item 36)
- The Johnstown Flood Centennial Project (Box 49, Item 37)
- The Case for Manufacturing in America's Future, 1988 (Box 49, Item 38)
- Upstairs, Downstairs: Class Conflict in an Employee Owned Factory by Jeremy Brecher (Box 49, Item 39)
- New York University of Law & Social Change, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Item 40)
- Employee Ownership: An Economic Development Tool for Anchoring Capital in Local Communities (Box 49, Item 41)
- Preliminary Recommendations of Community/Worker Ownership Structure for Reopened Campbell Works by Brad Dewan and Karl Frieden (Box 49, Item 42)
- Keep it Open News, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Item 43)
- Local Options for Economic Development in a Maturing Industrial Region by Roger S. Ahlbrandt, Jr. and James P. DeAngelis, 1987 (Box 49, Item 44)
- Steel on the Industrial Staircase: Conceptual Model for Early Warning to Other Industries and Nations, 1988 (Box 49, Item 45)
- Tri-State Annual Report, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- South Side Outreach: Churches (Box 50, Folder 2)
- South Side Outreach: Unions (Box 50, Folder 3)
- South Side Outreach: Businesses (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Electric Polka Benefit (Box 50, Folder 5)
- South Side Outreach: Community Groups (Box 50, Folder 6)
- South Side Outreach: Resolutions of Support (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
- Organizations and Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Book Chapters (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Raffle Tickets (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 50, Folder 14)
- CMP Newsletter, October 1988 (Box 50, Item 1)
- The Job Growth Centers of Allegheny County - Interim Report for the Project: Linking the Unemployed to Growth Centers in Allegheny County, 1989 (Box 50, Item 2)
- United Steelworkers of America Officers' Report, 1988 (Box 50, Item 3)
- Planning with People: Recent Pittsburgh Experience by Robert T. Norman (Box 50, Item 4)
- Economic Transformation in the Pittsburgh PMSA by Joan Fitzgerald Ely, 1979-1986 (Box 50, Item 5)
- "The World Can No Longer Afford the Rich" Pin (Box 50, Item 6)
- Organizing Your Community for Political Action by the United Steelworkes of America (Box 50, Item 7)
- CAS/Business Dual Major Program Description at the University of Pittsburgh (Box 50, Item 8)
- America's Steel Industry: A Time to Act (Box 50, Item 9)
- A Few Things You Should Know About Steel by Jones & Laughlin (Box 50, Item 10)
- Responding to Economic Dislocation, 1988 (Box 50, Item 11)
- The Overlook, April-May 1990 (Box 50, Item 12)
- Dun & Bradstreet's Guide to $Your Investments$ by Nancy Dunnan, 1988 (Box 50, Item 13)
- Newsletters by Neighborhood Organizations (Box 50, Item 14)
- Proposal for Reform of the Economic Development Zone Program, 1990 (Box 50, Item 15)
- Local Organization Information Cards (Box 50, Item 16)
- Check Stubs (Box 50, Item 17)
- Steel City Blues (Box 50, Cassette 1)
- Abortion: For Survival (Box 50, Cassette 2)
- Information on the Contract between the City of Pittsburgh and Tri-State regarding MAGLEV Research (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Three Rivers Community Fund, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Needmor, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- National Community Fund, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Needmor Grant Balance, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Ottenger Fund Matching Grant, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Presbyterian Hunger Fund, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Bydale Foundation (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Pittsburgh, Community Development Block Grant (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1986-1990 (Box 51, Folder 11-16)
- Community Development Corporation (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 18-26)
- Discount Foundation (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Coalition for Human Needs (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Episcopal, Coalition for Human Needs, Regional Reindustrialization Programs (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Gund Fund (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Heinz Endowment (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Jewish Fund for Justice (Box 51, Folder 32)
- United Jewish Foundation (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Joint Foundation Support (Box 51, Folder 34-35)
- Laurel Foundation (Box 51, Folder 36)
- Lilly Endowment (Box 51, Folder 37)
- C.S. Mott (Box 51, Folder 38)
- National Community Fund (Box 51, Folder 39-40)
- Needmor Fund (Box 51, Folder 41-42)
- New World Foundation (Box 51, Folder 43-44)
- Norman Foundation (Box 51, Folder 45)
- J.C Penny Foundation (Box 51, Folder 46-47)
- Ottinger Foundation (Box 51, Folder 48-49)
- Presbyterian (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Stern Foundation (Box 51, Folder 51)
- Ohio and Pennsylvania State Taxes, 1985-1990 (Box 52, Folder 1-12)
- City and Municipal Tax Returns, 1983-1992 (Box 52, Folder 13-29)
- Insurance, Property (Box 52, Folder 30-36)
- Health and Dental Insurance and Benefits (Box 52, Folder 37-48)
- Equipment (Box 52, Folder 49-51)
- Dislocated Workers Database (Box 52, Folder 52-53)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, Mechanisms (Box 52, Folder 54)
- City Pride (Box 52, Folder 55-70)
- Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Organizations (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Tri-State and Steel Valley Authority (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Contact List (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 53, Folder 8)
- The Ad Hoc Plant Closings Coalition (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Plant Closures Project (Box 53, Folder 10)
- News Releases (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Business Plan (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Buyout Committee (Box 53, Folder 14)
- LTV Buyout Committee: Environmental Waste (Box 53, Folder 15)
- LTV Buyout Comittee: Environmental Protection Agency Material (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Recharge South Side Steel Diagrams (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Recharge South Side Steel Fact Sheet, September 1988 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Recharge South Side Steel Financing (Box 53, Folder 19)
- LTV Buyout Committee: City Council Historical Designation (Box 53, Folder 20)
- LTV Buyout Committee: Investors and Customers (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Recharge South Side Steel: IPSCO, Inc. (Box 53, Folder 22)
- LTV Buyout Committee: Lazard-Freres Material (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Recharge South Side Steel: LTV Bankruptcy (Box 53, Folder 24-25)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Contract with United Steelworkers of America (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Recharge South Side Steel: LTV Negotiations (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Management Team (Box 53, Folder 28)
- Recharge South Side Steel Maps (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Map Transparencies (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Technology, 1990 (Box 53, Item 1)
- Clark Candy (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Emery Worldwide (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
- Industrial Cooperative Association (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Grogan, Graffam, McGinley & Lucchino, P.C. on Employee Stock Ownership Programs (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Steel Heritage: Johnstown (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Steel Heritage: Rankin (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Steel Heritage: Pittsburgh History Center (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Strategy 21: River Cities Coalition (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Strategy 21: Working Group Urban Principles (Box 54, Folder 10)
- State of Pennsylvania: Budget Lobbying, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Economic Development Models, Economic Disaster Prevent Shield (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Community Development Corporation: Advisory Commission on Community Based Organizations Proposal (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Community Development Corporation: New Vision Conference (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Community Development Corporation: Strategies for Progress (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Community Development Corporation: JPTA/DART Proposal - Brandow (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Steel Heritage: America's Industrial Heritage Project (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Steel Heritage: Draft Action Plan (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Steel Heritage: Economic Development Committee (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Steel Heritage: Economic Development/Tourism Committee (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Steel Heritage: Homestead, 1892 Centennial Labor Committee (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Economic Development Models: New Vision Community Development Corporations (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Steel Valley Authority: Early Warning Systems (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Document: Early Warning Information (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Working Group on Community Development - Airport: Background Material (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Working Group on Community Development - Airport (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Working Group on Community Development - Airport: Linking Growth Conference (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Working Group on Community Development - Airport: Revenue Sharing (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Airport: General Electric Co./Blawnox Agreement (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Industrial Cooperative Association (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Roundtable of Southwest Pennsylvania (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Federation of Industrial Retention and Renewal (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Potential Sources of Capitalization (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Steel Valley Authority Economic Development Employment Survey, Final Report (Box 54, Item 1)
- Greater Pittsburgh International Airport Impact Area Plan: An Agenda for Development, 1988 (Box 54, Item 2)
- Airport Area Economic Development: Final Report, May 1990 (Box 54, Item 3)
- An Agenda For Development: Greater Pittsburgh international Airport Impact Area Plan Appendix A and B, 1988 (Box 54, Item 4)
- Monetary Policy Objectives for 1987: Midyear Review of the Federal Reserve Board, July 21, 1987 (Box 54, Item 5)
- Community Economics, 1987 (Box 54, Item 6-7)
- AARP Highlights, July 1987 (Box 54, Item 8)
- 501(c)(3) Monthly Letter, August-November 1987, January 1988 (Box 54, Item 9-13)
- The Tri-State Peace & Justice Journal, May 1987 (Box 54, Item 14)
- Senior Pittsburgh, May 1987 (Box 54, Item 15)
- Allegheny Business News, November 1986 (Box 54, Item 16)
- Building the New Economy: States in the Lead by David R. Jones, 1986 (Box 54, Item 17)
- The AFL-CIO American Federationist, January 8, 1983 (Box 54, Item 18)
- This is the AFL-CIO (Box 54, Item 19)
- Defending America Without War (Box 54, Item 20)
- A View from the Valley (Box 54, Item 21)
- A Special Report: Summary USWA/LTV Steel Corp. Proposed Agreement (Box 54, Item 22)
- Building on the Basics: The Final Report of the Mayor's Task Force on Steel and Southeast Chicago (Box 54, Item 23)
- This Land is Home to Me: A Pastoral Letter on Powerlessness in Appalachia by the Catholic Bishops of the Region, May 17, 1985 (Box 54, Item 24)
- Making Steel at J&L with Jake & Looey, 1979 (Box 54, Item 25)
- Plant Closing: Advance Notice and Rapid Response, 1986 (Box 54, Item 26)
- Federation for Industrial Retention & Renewal News, January 1989 (Box 54, Item 27)
- Arc Allegheny: Partners With a Purpose, Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Item 28)
- Interreligious Economic Crisis Organizing Network Newsletter, 1986 (Box 54, Item 29)
- Jobs Impact Bulletin, December 1986, April-May 1987 (Box 54, Item 30-31)
- LTV in Bankruptcy: A Preliminary Appraisal by R.D. Smith & Company, Inc. (Box 54, Item 32)
- Pittsburgh High Technology, July-August 1987 (Box 54, Item 33)
- The New People by the Thomas Merton Center, February 1988 (Box 54, Item 34)
- Proposal for a Neighborhood Development Corporation (Box 54, Item 35)
- Shaping Our Future: A Community Vision for Pittsburgh Regional Development, 1987 (Box 54, Item 36)
- The Steelworkers Oldtimer, 1986 (Box 54, Item 37)
- Amsteel: A Positive Response to LTV Bankruptcy, The Attack on Retiree Pensions and Benefits and the Collapse of American Industry, 1987 (Box 54, Item 38)
- Steel Valley Authority v. Union Switch and Signal Division, American Standard, Inc. et al., 1987 (Box 54, Item 39)
- Rapid Response Under EDWAA: ETA Perspective and Expectations, March 10, 1989 (Box 54, Item 40)
- Justice Speaks: Black Workers for Justice, April 1989 (Box 54, Item 41)
- Veatch, 1986-1990 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
- Wellspring (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Underhill Foundation (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Unitarians, Veatch (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Wellspring Funders Conference, May 16, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Wellspring Fund (Box 55, Folder 7)
- World Vision (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Youth Project (Box 55, Folder 9)
- The Youth Project Donor Fund (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Duquesne Light Economic Development Fund (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Tri-State Finances and Taxes (Box 55, Folder 12-35)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Metals Retention Study (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Press (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Metals Retention Study Summary (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Scrap (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Social Impact Study (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Songer Corporation Bid Proposal (Box 56, Folder 6)
- By-Laws of South Side Steel of Pittsburgh, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Technical Information (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Steel Making Processes (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Center for Metals Production (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Steel Valley Authory Role/Bonds/Lease (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Transportation Issues (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Recharge South Side Steel: Lawrence Weeks Contract (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans: Steel Valley Authority Survey Contract and Final Report (Box 56, Folder 14-15)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans: Steel Valley Authority Survey Report, July 1988 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Economic Development Organizations: Industrial Cooperative Association (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Economic Development Organizations: Mountain Association for Community Economic Development, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Economic Development Organizations: Midwest Center for Labor Research (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Economic Development Organizations: National Committee for Full Employment (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Economic Development Organizations: Naugutuck Valley (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Economic Development Organizations: New York Job Development Authority (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Economic Development Organizations: Northeast Ohio Employee Ownership Center (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Economic Development Organizations: Plant Closures Project (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Economic Development Organizations: Pennsylvania Caucus on Jobs & Justice (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Mon Valley Players: Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Mon Valley Players: Steel Valley Planning Commission (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Mon Valley Players: Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Mon Valley Players: Steel Valley Council of Governments (Box 56, Folder 29)
- Mon Valley Players: Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Community Development Corporation: Working Group on Community Development (Box 56, Folder 31)
- Buy-Out Committee c/o United Steelworkers of America, Preliminary Draft Bid Specifications, 1988 (Box 56, Item 1)
- Technoeconomic Assessment of Electric Steelmaking Through the Year 2000, October 1987 (Box 56, Item 2)
- Mon Valley Players (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Mon Valley Players: Western Pennsylvania Advanced Technology Center (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Economic Development Organizations: Alliance for a Better Tomorrow (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Economic Development Organizations: Center for Popular Economics (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Economic Development Organizations: Economic Policy Institute (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Allegheny County (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Allegheny County: Strategy 21 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Community Development Corporations: Bloomfield-Garfield Corporation (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Community Development Corporations: Duquesne (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Community Development Corporations: Homestead (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Community Development Corporations: Lawrenceville Development Corporation (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Community Development Corporations: McKeesport (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Community Development Corporations: Mon Valley Development Team (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Community Development Corporations: Pittsburgh, Hill District (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Community Development Corporations: Pittsburgh, North Side (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Community Development Corporations: Rankin (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Community Development Corporations Information (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Mon Valley Players: The Enterprise Foundation (Box 57, Folder 18)
- Mon Valley Players: Mon-Ohio Commission (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Mon Valley Players: Mid-Mon Valley Economic Revitalization Program (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Mon Valley Players: Mon Valley Commission (Box 57, Folder 21)
- Mon Valley Players: Mon Valley Network (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Mon Valley Players: Mon Valley Progress Council (Box 57, Folder 23)
- Mon Valley Players: Project for Economic Renewal of Communities (Box 57, Folder 24)
- Mon Valley Players: Pittsburgh High Technology Center (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Mon Valley Players: Regional Research, Inc. (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Mon Valley Players: Allegheny Conference on Community Development (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Mon Valley Players: Regional Industrial Development Corporation (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Tri-State Board Meetings (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Tri-State Board Finances (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Tri-State Board Newsletter (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Tri-State Board Strategic Planning (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Tri State Staff, Job Descriptions (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Tri State Staff, Personnel Policy (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Tri State Staff Time Sheets (Box 57, Folder 35-36)
- Tri State Staff Weekly Reports (Box 57, Folder 37)
- Speeches (Box 57, Folder 38)
- Workers Compensation (Box 57, Folder 39)
- External Contacts (Box 57, Folder 40)
- Federation of Southern Cooperatives, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh Annual Report, 1986 (Box 57, Item 1)
- The South Pittsburgh Reporter, June 28, 1988, May 2 and September 19, 1989 (Box 57, Item 2-4)
- Senior Pittsburgh, May 1989 (Box 57, Item 5)
- Centennial Reports (Box 57, Item 6)
- International Publishers Book Newsletter and Full Catalog, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Item 7)
- Italy's Industrial Renaissance: A Strategy for Developing Small Manufacturing Business, October 21-22, 1986 (Box 57, Item 8)
- The Entrepreneurial Economy, July-August 1987 (Box 57, Item 9)
- Boycott Shell Bulletin (Box 57, Item 10)
- Just Harvest News, June-July 1988 (Box 57, Item 11)
- Advance Summary: State and Local Initiatives on Plant Closings and Public Subsidies, April 15, 1989 (Box 57, Item 12)
- Experiments in Employment - A British Cure by John E. Schwarz and Thomas J. Volgy (Box 57, Item 13)
- Plant Closings: Information on Advance Notice and Assistance to Dislocated Workers (Box 57, Item 14)
- Jobs with Peace Campaign Report, 1988 (Box 57, Item 15)
- Jobs Impact Bulletin, July 1987 (Box 57, Item 16)
- Keep It Open News, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Item 17)
- Small Business Planning Guide (Box 57, Item 18)
- The Overlook, August-September 1988 (Box 57, Item 19)
- Senior Citizens News and Views, August 1987 (Box 57, Item 20)
- AARP Highlights, January-February 1986 (Box 57, Item 21)
- Newspaper Clippings and Articles (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
- Part III - Corporations Not-For-Profit (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Italia Artiganata - The Third Italy: A New Model for Economic Democracy (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Organizations (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Trade Union Housing Corporation (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Pennsylvania Historic Resource Survey of LTV Steel in Pittsburgh (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Tri-State and Steel Valley Authority (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Registrants (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Packet (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Panelists' Papers (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Workshops Summary and List (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Post Conference Letter and List (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Executive Summary (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Conference Report (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Draft Material for Report (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Thank Yous (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Lynn Williams Speech (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Reports (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Summary Reports (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Budget (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Brochure (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Invitees (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Project Definition (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Conference Questionnaires (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Meeting, March 9, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Industrial Renaissance Project Meeting, December 7, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Federation of Industrial Retention and Renewal Requests for Assistance, March 9, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Board Recommendations, April 23, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Industrial Renaissance Project: Program Inventory (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference Workshop Recordings (Box 58, Cassette 1-8)
- "Save Switch & Brake" Poster (Box 58, Item 1)
- Executive Summary, Business and Industrial Development Corporations (Box 58, Item 2)
- Plant Closings: New Roles for Policymakers by John Portz, 1989 (Box 58, Item 3)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: List of Participants, September 14-15, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Invites to Participants (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Press (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference: Registration Packets (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Industrial Roundtable Meeting, November 15, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)